comptechdoc.org 2005-03-08

# Our Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we are providing this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. 

### Collected Information

At this website you can submit and rate links, documentation, and post to a forum. When submitting links or documentation, the types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include your name, your e-mail address and optional phone number and website information which may be sent in non secure mode over the internet when applying for membership or changing settings. The submission of your phone number is optional. Your e-mail may be used to contact you with special information about this site or your acount. Your phone number may be used to contact you with permission about work associated with this site. 

### Third Party Distribution

**No personal information including your real name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or any other information collected will be given to any third party for any reason.**

### Your ability to correct or access information

When using your membership we allow changes to your email address, phone number, and password along with the optional web site name and description. 

### Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

### Cookies

To enhance your experience with this site, some of our web pages use \\\\\"cookies.\\\\\" Cookies are text files we place in your computer\\\\\'s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. Once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information is linked to the data stored in the cookie to make it easier for you to access your account. No information is collected on this site for marketing purposes or to attempt to track use of the internet outside this site.
